{
    "subject": "resource/Duke_George_of_Oldenburg",
    "predicate": "ontology/parent",
    "object": "resource/Duchess_Frederica_of_W\u00fcrttemberg",
    "human_readable": "Duke George of Oldenburg's parent is Duchess Frederica of W\u00fcrttemberg.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9878358244895935,
            "question": "Is Duke George of Oldenburg related to Duchess Frederica of W\u00fcrttemberg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9621021151542664,
            "question": "To whom is Duchess Frederica of W\u00fcrttemberg a parent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9618561267852783,
            "question": "Who is the parent of Duke George of Oldenburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9507834315299988,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Duke George of Oldenburg and Duchess Frederica of W\u00fcrttemberg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9283608198165894,
            "question": "Is Duke George of Oldenburg a duke?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9227220416069031,
            "question": "Who is Duchess Frederica of W\u00fcrttemberg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8994482755661011,
            "question": "Which royal family does Duchess Frederica of W\u00fcrttemberg belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8947258591651917,
            "question": "What is the name of Duke George of Oldenburg's mother?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7337931990623474,
            "question": "What is the name of Duchess Frederica's son?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6260213851928711,
            "question": "What is the name of the region where Duke George of Oldenburg rules?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Duke George of Oldenburg's parent is Duchess Frederica of W\u00fcrttemberg.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7171_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Duchess Frederica's son?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7171_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Duke George of Oldenburg's mother?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7171_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which royal family does Duchess Frederica of W\u00fcrttemberg belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7171_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7171_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7171_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7171_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7171_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7171_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7171_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7171_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7171_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7171_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7171_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that Duke George of Oldenburg's mother is indeed Duchess Frederica of W\u00fcrttemberg. This is explicitly stated in multiple documents, including `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7171/re-ranker-msmarco/42.txt` and `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7171/re-ranker-msmarco/60.txt`."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in the documents, which state that Duchess Frederica of W\u00fcrttemberg was indeed George\u2019s mother. Therefore, she is his parent as claimed in the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}